Alright so the last time, we have created the loan all, we see all tabs, active tab,
there are some patterns, images, and extractable so we see 19 tables.
This way, I will try to make it more simplified such as us again, please.
Allow me to check about the tables.
I want a simplified UI, but maybe,
and remove all other action artists.
Just leave panel for tables.
So it will remove, and after that as well, it will try to apply it.
And in that case, it has four to the list, our open new agent,
and I will use simple musto null there.
And actually, I will use that script. So this is created on older,
and I want to have this kind of stuff created on the dialog.
So we can try, this is the active tab, there are some filters,
but I just want to create the null dialog. This is only what I want, so I will just use this.
And besides that, we can scan check first sources, replace some occurrences.
But for now, just use that one part.
Add this quick download dialog at the top, so the tables will be below.
Okay, now it should add a new thing.
Okay, so the quick downloader appears on the top. Now just refresh my extension,
so I'm going back, pressing it, and yeah, I see a nice design and nice table.
This is what I want, I want to simplify it, so users will be able to quickly extract all of the files.
Now open random page, it can be word population.
It can be this, and now when I press it, there are some images,
we see some images, PNGs, and we can download now. So if I want to download,
PNGs, I can say download now, and it's automatically download.
So word population counter, let me find, okay, this is in like Westworkshire,
and there are zero GIFs, there are some HTML files and some tables that automatically
detect, I love it, it's pretty simple, and this is what I want.